Hey everybody, welcome to another
English listening quiz. This quiz will
test your listening comprehension skills
and help you learn the real sounds of
English. But before we start, remember
to download the Listening Time podcast
and click on the link in the description
below this video to become a Listening
Time member and you'll receive my
listening practice seminars, which will
help you understand native speakers when
they speak fast. And if you become a
Listening Time family member, then
you'll get my advanced podcast episodes,
which will help you reach an advanced
level of listening. Okay, let's start
with the quiz. Here's the first
question. Which of these am I saying?
19 nights
The correct answer is B. The number 19
is pronounced 19 with a T sound. Listen
again. 19 nights. The number 90 is
pronounced 90 with a D sound. Listen
again. 90 nights. 19 nights, 90 nights.
All right, here's the next question.
Which of these words am I saying? sheet
The correct answer is D. Listen to the
difference between each word. First, we
have cheap with a ch sound and a long e
sound, cheap. Next, we have chip with a
ch sound and a short i sound, chip.
Next, we have ship with a sh sound and a
short i sound, ship. And lastly, we have
sheep with a sh sound and a long e
sound, sheep. Cheap, chip, ship, sheep.
Okay, next question. What's the third
word that I'm saying in this sentence? A
cup of noodles sounds good.
The third word in that sentence is of.
Listen again. A cup of noodles sounds
good. The word of is often reduced to a
in English. Instead of saying a cup of
noodles, we say a cup of noodles. All
right, last question. What sentence am I
saying? There's never been a better time
for it.
Write your answer in a comment down
below. Okay, before we go, remember to
download the Listening Time podcast and
become a Listening Time member to
receive my specialized training, which
will help you understand fast English.
And if you want my advanced podcast
episodes, then become a Listening Time
family member. Click on the link in the
description below this video to sign up.
Also, remember to subscribe to the
channel, click on the bell, and follow
us on Instagram. I'll see you next time.